this is the talk that you're in I hope
这是你希望的话题
you you are where you expect to be my
你你是你期望成为我的地方
name is John Schneider I'm from the
我叫约翰·施耐德（John Schneider）
engineering tools team and internal
工程工具团队和内部
tools team at Netflix I'm Taylor Witt
Netflix的工具团队我是Taylor Witt
self and the billing and payments team
自我以及帐单和付款团队
in that voice today what we're going to
在今天的声音中，我们将要
be showing you is how to take a simple
向您展示如何简单
canonical spring boot web service and
规范的Spring Boot Web服务和
turning it into a cloud ready service so
将其转变为云就绪服务
we're going to do is we're going to take
我们将要做的是
that simple spring boot service and
简单的spring boot服务以及
we're going to incrementally add
我们将逐步添加
cloud-ready features some of which you
具备云端功能的功能
may have seen before
可能以前看过
and some I promise you haven't seen
还有一些我保证你没有看过
before we'll start out with adding a
在我们开始添加一个
service discovery and explaining why you
服务发现并解释您的原因
you want to do that we'll add client
您想要这样做，我们将添加客户端
side load balancing and ribbon move over
侧负载平衡和功能区移动
to just a little brief bit about Fame
只是关于名声的一点点
and then the circuit breaker pattern
然后是断路器模式
with history and we'll will follow up
历史，我们将跟进
with how we do a tag based metrics
我们如何基于标签的指标
collection and reporting and show you
收集和报告并向您展示
how to generate some nice visuals from
如何从中产生一些漂亮的视觉效果
the atlas metrics back in towards the
地图集指标又回到了
end so every bit of code we're going to
结束，所以我们要编写的每一段代码
show you is already on github we have an
显示您已经在github上了
organization we've built just for this
我们为此建立的组织
called netflix spring one if you don't
如果你不叫netflix的 Spring 一
like to follow along start out with
喜欢跟着开始
these three sample projects sample
这三个样本项目样本
eureka sample membership and sample
尤里卡（Eureka）样品成员资格和样品
recommendations and since the head of
建议和自负责人以来
all these repositories is the final
所有这些存储库都是最终的
answer so to speak you know with all the
回答，可以这么说，
pieces integrated if you do want to
如果您想集成件
follow along in the sample
跟随样本
recommendations project check out the
推荐项目签出
start tag because we'll be we'll be
开始标记，因为我们将成为
working exclusively on the
专为
recommendations project and adding
推荐项目并添加
functionality today to that as we go
今天的功能，随着我们的前进
along last little bit of a admin note
沿着管理员笔记的最后一点
here is if you again if you do want to
如果您愿意，这是如果您再次
follow along once you call in these
一旦你打电话给这些
repos go ahead and start Eureka and
回购继续并启动尤里卡和
start membership you can do that either
开始成为会员，您既可以这样做
from the command line through Gradle W
从命令行通过Gradle W
boot run or if you stuck them into an
开机运行，或者如果您将它们卡在
IDE just run the main method in both
IDE只是在两者中都运行main方法
so just to describe the API we're gonna
因此，为了描述我们要使用的API
be building today we're going to take
今天要建设，我们要采取
the role of the recommendations team at
建议小组的职责
Netflix so it's gonna be a very slim
Netflix，它将变得非常苗条
down example but the recommendation
倒的例子，但建议
service is going to make a call to the
服务将致电给
membership service to fetch some
会员服务取一些
information about a customer in our
有关我们客户的信息
example we're gonna get the age and
例如，我们要确定年龄并
we're gonna use that data to feed into
我们将使用这些数据输入
what kind of recommendations we return
我们返回什么样的建议
so if we just shift over to the code
因此，如果我们只是转到代码
aspect of this demo you can see it's a
该演示的一个方面，您可以看到它是一个
regular old spring boot application
常规的旧 spring boot 应用程序
we're using the the one class style
我们使用的是一类风格
we're defining a bean of rest template
我们正在定义其余的模板模板
we're defining one rest endpoint API
我们正在定义一个休息端点API
recommendations slash user to which
建议将用户削减到
we're going to respond by calling the
我们将通过拨打
membership service which is running on
正在运行的会员服务
our localhost port 8000 we're going to
我们的 localhost 端口8000
check the age of any given customer that
检查任何给定客户的年龄
comes in and we're going to return
进来，我们要回来
recommendations based on that so anyone
基于此的建议，因此任何人
under 17 get some kid recommendations
17岁以下儿童推荐
anyone above gets the adult regular
以上任何人都会有成人
catalog and of course we have some just
目录，当然我们有一些
Lombok here to flesh out the data model
Lombok在这里充实数据模型
so we're gonna go ahead and start this
所以我们要开始
guy up
家伙起来
common spring food application and then
常见的 Spring 食品应用
we're gonna go and look at some of our
我们要去看一些
infrastructure make sure that is yes so
基础设施确保是这样
we do have eureka running we do have the
我们确实有尤里卡运行，我们确实有
membership service up but not
会员服务开通，但没有
recommendations and we're going to just
建议，我们将只
move on to figuring out how we're going
继续弄清楚我们要怎么做
to turn this into the style of
把它变成
application we would build at in Netflix
我们将在Netflix中构建的应用程序
so we have our business logic now we
现在我们有了业务逻辑
need some of the infrastructure magic
需要一些基础设施魔术
how's that
怎么样
so before we go too much further we're
所以在我们走得更远之前，我们是
just going to execute a few rest
只是要休息一下
requests against our our services that's
对我们的服务提出的要求是
running that we're gonna be operating
运行我们将要运行的
upon so just to demonstrate that it's
只是为了证明它是
that it's up and running I guess I gotta
它已经启动并运行了，我想我必须
hit the right port good start huh and
击中正确的端口，好开始吧，
sure enough so our recommendation
足够肯定，所以我们的建议
service is really simple
服务真的很简单
since the my service believes that I'm
因为我的服务相信我
10 years old it's gonna say that I
10岁那会说我
should watch The Lion King or frozen
应该看狮子王还是冰封的
that should be familiar Taylor since it
泰勒应该很熟悉
says he's 30 years old that's gonna give
说他要30岁
him some a couple different movie
他拍了几部不同的电影
recommendation it's gonna say he should
建议，他会说他应该
watch the Shawshank Redemption or this
看肖申克的救赎或这个
blockbuster film we've heard about
我们听说过的大片
called spring so that's it it's really
叫做 Spring ，就是这样
simple service and this is a good point
简单的服务，这是一个好点
to say that this I this could basically
说，这我基本上可以
be packaged into a war and deployed to
被打包成战争并部署到
tomcat in a data center you know on
在您了解的数据中心中的tomcat
websphere WebLogic or anything like that
websphere WebLogic或类似的东西
so to any organization that's starting
所以对于任何刚开始的组织
they're starting in a data center that's
他们开始在一个数据中心
starting you know you know on kind of
开始你知道你知道某种
legacy platforms like that this is your
像这样的旧平台
starting point and Netflix wasn't that
起点，而不是Netflix
different we're not that old of a
不一样，我们还不算老
company we just started streaming at all
公司，我们才刚刚开始流式传输
and in the mid-2000s and we didn't start
在2000年代中期，我们没有开始
making a cloud migration until after
进行云迁移，直到之后
2010 so a lot of way you're gonna see
2010年您将看到的很多方式
today is really just things that have
今天真的只是拥有的东西
really emerged in the last five or so
真的出现在最后五个左右
years and and how we've learned from
年，以及我们如何从中学到
that and so without further ado we'll do
这样，事不宜迟，我们会做
the first thing which is adding Eureka
首先是添加尤里卡
if you're following along we're gonna
如果您关注我们，我们将
first go to the Gradle script that we've
首先转到我们已经拥有的Gradle脚本
got for the recommendations project and
获得推荐项目，
you'll see this pattern over and over
您会一遍又一遍地看到这种模式
again with with spring cloud we're gonna
再次与 Spring 的云，我们要
add a dependency on org uh Spring
添加对org uh Spring的依赖
Framework dot cloud
框架点云
spring clouds starter Eureka a really
Spring 的云启动器尤里卡真的
easy name to remember and will refresh
容易记住的名字，会刷新
our gradle dependencies to be sure that
我们的gradle依赖项可以确保
that we get that new dependency while
我们得到了新的依赖
we're waiting for that the only property
我们在等那唯一的财产
that we need to get this service
我们需要获得这项服务
communicating with Eureka upfront it's
与尤里卡沟通，这是
just the location of the Eureka service
只是尤里卡服务的位置
itself so we're gonna say that the
本身，所以我们要说
client service URL
客户服务网址
is here
在这儿
notice I've got Eureka running on my own
注意，我已经自己运行了尤里卡
machine so again you know if you're
机器，所以再次知道你是否
starting one of the things you're going
开始你要去的事情之一
to notice if you're starting in a day
通知您一天是否开始
center you're starting you know not
你开始的中心，你不知道
knock you know in a cloud platform right
在云平台上敲你知道的权利
now is all the pieces that we have all
现在是我们拥有的所有碎片
the pieces that we're going to show you
我们将向您展示的碎片
can be ran on this laptop and will be
可以在这台笔记本电脑上运行
ran on this laptop so they can be ran
在此笔记本电脑上运行，因此可以运行
anywhere they can be ran in a center
他们可以在中心跑的任何地方
they can be ran in AWS or GCE anywhere
它们可以在任何地方的AWS或GCE中运行
at all and for the purpose of a
完全是为了
demonstration a little later on here
稍后再示范
we're going to add an instance host name
我们将添加一个实例主机名
to it we'll call it the one the one and
为此，我们将其称为“一对一”，
only recommendation service that we're
我们唯一的推荐服务
going to be running today by default
默认情况下今天将运行
spring cloud will choose the host name
Spring Cloud将选择主机名
as the host name of your machine since
作为您的计算机的主机名，因为
we're going to be executing some rest
我们要去休息一下
requests against Eureka server itself we
针对Eureka服务器本身的请求
want to give it a name that's
想要给它起一个名字
predictable and internally and that's
在内部是可预测的，那就是
what's we usually set this since we're
我们通常设置什么，因为
in Amazon to the Amazon instance ID just
在Amazon中仅将Amazon实例ID
anything that's unique globally identify
全球独一无二的任何事物
one represents your one server instance
一个代表您的一个服务器实例
lastly we just add an able eureka client
最后，我们只添加一个有能力的尤里卡客户
on the spring brewed application so this
在 Spring 酿造的应用程序上，所以这
is the first step in making it cloud
是使它成云的第一步
ready and because we're not quite ready
准备好了，因为我们还没有准备好
to show ribbon client-side
显示功能区客户端
load-balancing yet we're gonna add a
负载平衡，但我们要添加一个
primary annotation to this rest template
其余模板的主要注释
so that the existing functionality still
这样现有功能仍然
works the when we use the rest template
使用其余模板时有效
to execute a request against our fake
对我们的假货执行请求
membership service then it's still going
会员服务，然后它仍在继续
to execute using the regular DNS name
使用常规DNS名称执行
and not try to use your we gonna do so
而不是尝试使用您会使用的
so we're going to start up
所以我们要开始
recommendations again
再次推荐
and now when we go over into Springs
现在当我们进入斯普林斯
lovely Eureka server dashboard here we
可爱的尤里卡服务器仪表板在这里我们
see that we have two services running
看到我们有两个服务正在运行
membership and recommendations and you
成员资格和推荐，还有您
see that the instance name for the one
看到一个的实例名称
and only recommendations instance is
并且只有推荐实例是
indeed the one so this is this is the
确实是一个，所以这就是
starting point right here one thing to
起点就在这里一件事
note so we started out here right we
注意，所以我们从这里开始
started out with just two services one
一开始只有两项服务
executing against another via some fixed
通过一些固定的对另一个执行
DNS name we do want to point out that
我们确实要指出的DNS名称
this isn't entirely different from an
这与
environment like this where maybe you're
这样的环境，也许你在
running multiple instances of the
运行多个实例
membership service and you put them
会员服务，你把他们
behind some sort of load balancer if
在某种负载均衡器后面
you're an AWS that would be an elastic
你是一个有弹性的AWS
load balancer and then you you put a
负载均衡器，然后您将
route 53 DNS name on that that ELB so
在该ELB上路由53 DNS名称，因此
that it's got a you know a fixed name
它有一个你知道一个固定的名字
and you execute against that route 53
然后您执行那条路线53
provided DNS name this is a pretty
提供的DNS名称，这是一个漂亮的
common paradigm I think this is a this
常见范式我认为这是一个
is something you'll find in the wild
你会在野外找到的东西
quite a bit well we've just done is
我们刚刚做的很好
we've taken this and we've eliminated
我们已经接受了，我们已经淘汰了
the two pieces in the middle so we're
中间的两块，所以我们
ready now to add a client-side load
现在准备添加客户端负载
balancer that allows the recommendation
平衡器，可以推荐
service to execute requests directly
直接执行请求的服务
against effectively directly against the
直接反对
membership service without having to
会员服务，而不必
define additional pieces of
定义其他部分
infrastructure like load balancers and
负载平衡器和
route 53 addresses and so forth for
路线53地址，依此类推
every every service that you provide in
您提供的每一项服务
your in your micro service architecture
您在您的微服务架构中
what this also gains us is the ability
这也给我们带来的是能力
to plug in additional operational
插入其他操作
insights right up front so when we want
洞察力就在我们前面
to go to add a circuit breaker dashboard
去添加断路器仪表板
that circuit breaker can refer to all
该断路器可以引用所有
the service instances running in your
在您的服务器上运行的服务实例
micro service architecture by just
微服务架构
querying your eco server and getting all
查询您的生态服务器并获得全部
the instances when you want to run a
您想运行的实例
piece of delivery automation you know
您知道的交付自动化
like Asgard or spinnaker which will tell
例如Asgard或大三角帆
you that later
你那以后
again that can execute requests against
再次可以执行针对
Eureka when you want to develop a
尤里卡当你想开发一个
metrics back-end that shows you certain
指标后端，向您显示出一定的
statistics about every service that's
有关每个服务的统计信息
running in your organization
在您的组织中运行
that can be done again versus Eureka if
如果可以的话，可以与尤里卡再次进行
you're a back here in this realm where
你回到了这个领域
you had load balancers and things like
你有负载均衡器之类的东西
that that you're configuring once per
您每个配置一次
service you also have to be able to
服务，您还必须能够
itemize all those services for every one
逐项列出所有这些服务
of these pieces of operational insight
这些运营洞察力
that you try to gain so this is a key
你试图获得的，所以这是关键
benefit of service discovery so one of
服务发现的好处，所以其中之一
the other items that doesn't get talked
其他不说话的项目
about very often when we talk about
大约在我们谈论的时候
eureka is okay we have service discovery
尤里卡很好，我们有服务发现
we have load balancing but how do we
我们有负载平衡，但我们如何
enable testing and how do we enable
启用测试以及我们如何启用
rollouts so Netflix commonly uses a
推出，因此Netflix通常使用
red-black strategy right we have code
红黑策略对，我们有代码
running in production we don't want a
在生产中运行，我们不需要
downtime we want to pull up some new
停机时间，我们想拉起一些新的
code and we want to make sure that it's
代码，我们要确保它是
reasonably functional and then we want
合理的功能，然后我们想要
to disable the old code path but not
禁用旧代码路径，但不禁用
actually destroy the server's in AWS it
实际上在AWS中销毁了服务器
can take anywhere from five minutes to
可能需要五分钟到
15 minutes to bring up a new instance so
15分钟启动一个新实例
if we find an issue with our code and we
如果我们发现代码有问题，我们
need to recover quickly spinning up new
需要快速恢复发展新的
instances isn't going to happen so what
实例将不会发生，那又怎样
we will typically do is use discovery to
我们通常要做的是使用发现来
affect the the visibility status of a
影响某人的可见度状态
given instance so you can see my
给定实例，以便您可以看到我的
recommendation service is registered as
推荐服务注册为
up in discovery and I'm going to go
发现中，我要去
ahead and just influence that slightly
向前并稍微影响一下
so I'm just gonna make a curl to the
所以我只是要卷曲
Eureka service and I'm going to drop
尤里卡服务，我要去
this instance the the instanceid that is
这个实例的instanceid是
unique the one out of the
独一无二的
recommendations cluster I'm gonna put
我要放的推荐群组
them out of service there we go
他们失去服务了，我们去了
anybody using ribbon or any kind of
任何人使用色带或任何种类的
Eureka based load balancing would not be
基于Eureka的负载平衡不会
able to find this guy so great now he's
能够找到这个人，他现在很棒
disabled no traffic will go to him
残疾人，没有交通会去他
mission achieved we have red black well
任务实现了，我们的红黑很好
not quite I mean some of our services
不完全是我的意思，我们的一些服务
are arrest based but on other teams we
基于逮捕，但根据其他团队
have more than just rest based services
不仅仅是休息服务
billing and payments everything we do is
结算和付款，我们要做的就是
match or queue based so how do you
匹配或基于队列，那么您如何
enable red black based on something
根据某些情况启用红黑色
that's not not rest centric so a piece
那不是以休息为中心的，所以一块
we found missing from spring cloud which
我们发现 Spring Cloud 中缺少
we've added is the exactly that ability
我们添加的正是这种能力
the ability to react to your discovery
对发现做出反应的能力
status so I'm gonna go ahead and add
状态，所以我要继续添加
that dependency and we'll see how that
这种依赖关系，我们将看到
works for us
为我们工作
so it's gonna be under spring cloud
所以它会在 Spring 的云下
netflix contribute this is a library
netflix贡献这是一个图书馆
we've created just for the purposes of
我们仅出于以下目的创建
taking some of this internal code we've
采取一些内部代码，我们已经
been using for a while now at Spring
在Spring已经使用了一段时间
boot and just putting it out into the
启动，然后将其放入
light of day sharing with the community
与社区分享日光
I expect fully that this is going to be
我完全希望这将是
a temporary location for this code every
每个代码的临时位置
bit of this we really want to put into
这一点我们真的很想投入
pull requests for Spring cloud yes
拉取对Spring cloud的请求是
yeah no more internal wrappers at
是的，不再有内部包装器在
Netflix that only we know about we
只有我们知道的Netflix
commit to sharing what we've learned so
致力于分享我们所学到的东西
just refresh those dependencies let that
只需刷新那些依赖项，
come back and while that's going I'll go
回来，那边我会去
back to our recommendation service and
回到我们的推荐服务
what we want to do is start actually
我们要做的是实际上开始
coding against that event so easy enough
对该事件进行编码非常容易
Spring has event listeners now this is a
Spring 有事件监听器，这是一个
great improvement on on the spring
Spring 的大进步
application event patterns love this
应用程序事件模式喜欢这个
annotation kudos guys and the for to
批注大家和为
release for having this
为此发布
so we're just gonna code ourselves to a
所以我们只是将自己编码为
eureka status changed event for the sake
尤里卡状态改变事件
of simplicity I'm just gonna print out
简单起见，我只是打印出来
the result of this so this event will
结果，所以这个事件将
fire and return to me the current status
解雇并返回我的当前状态
not as my in my instance thanks but as
在我看来，不是我的感谢，而是
the rest of the world sees it so if the
世界其他地方都可以看到，如果
Discovery servers think this instance is
发现服务器认为该实例是
down or out of service that's what's
停机或服务中断是什么
going to be triggered here so if we just
将在这里被触发，所以如果我们只是
bounce that app
弹跳该应用程序
hopefully we should see Discovery thinks
希望我们应该看到Discovery的想法
we are out of service because I bounced
我们退役了，因为我弹跳了
it just fast enough that it thinks I
它足够快以至于我认为
didn't actually die and come back as a
并没有真正死掉，然后回来
new instance I'm the same instance who
新实例，我是谁
temporarily lost connection so let's see
暂时失去连接，让我们看看
if I can just shift that a bit so let's
如果我可以稍微改变一下，那么让我们
put him back into up if I go here I see
把他放回去，如果我去这里，我明白了
the status is up in Discovery and now
状态在“发现”中处于现在状态
we're just simply waiting for waiting
我们只是在等待
for this instance to recognize the fact
在这种情况下认识到事实
that is now so here we have the hook for
现在是这样，我们在这里有了
it this is where we're going to put in
这是我们要放入的地方
the actual CoreLogic
实际的CoreLogic
if you're on a listener container some
如果你在一个监听容器上
JMS container right container dot stop
JMS容器右侧容器点停止
if you're a spring integration fan
如果您是Spring 集成爱好者
control bus dot send
控制总线点发送
stop the channel as you're interested in
停止播放您感兴趣的频道
right if you are scheduled jobs you know
对，如果您是预定的工作，您知道
find the jobs disable them spring batch
找到工作禁用他们Spring Batch
kill any any recurring instances there
杀死那里的任何重复出现的实例
any running instances so now even though
现在任何正在运行的实例，即使
you're not just a rest central
你不只是休息的中心
application you can participate in red
可以参加红色的申请
black using discovery so that's that's
使用发现黑色，那就是
exactly how we do it at Netflix our
正是我们在Netflix上的做法
internal tooling when we say we want a
内部工具，当我们说我们想要一个
red black deployment will do this it'll
红黑部署会做到这一点
find the instances in the old codebase
在旧的代码库中找到实例
and disable them put them out of service
并禁用它们使它们停止服务
bring the new ones up let those take
提出新的，让那些
traffic if there's any batch stuff
交通，如果有任何批处理的东西
running in the background
在后台运行
those will get stopped by this
那些会被这个阻止
one of the things we love about the way
我们喜欢的方式之一
spring cloud has implemented the Eureka
Spring 的云实现了尤里卡
server integration itself is that it's
服务器集成本身就是
an annotation that you put on a spring
放在Spring 上的注释
boot out which at first blush you think
引导一下，乍一看你脸红
well that's not super useful why don't I
好吧，这不是超级有用，为什么我不
just download a binary and start the
只需下载二进制文件并启动
thing but what's interesting about this
事情，但是有趣的是
is since since you're you're decorating
因为自从你在装饰
us an existing spring boot app you can
我们可以使用现有的Spring Boot应用程序
start adding functionality to your eco
开始为您的生态系统添加功能
server that doesn't already exist so we
服务器尚不存在，所以我们
already talked about eureka servers use
已经谈论过尤里卡服务器的使用
in our automated deployment or automated
在我们的自动部署或自动
delivery pipelines right now you could
现在就可以交付管道了
take a you know a naval eureka server
带一个你知道海军尤里卡服务器
decorated spring boot application and
装饰的 spring boot 应用程序和
start adding endpoints to it tailored to
开始向其添加量身定制的端点
your types of deployment automation so
您的部署自动化类型，因此
you know you could add a red-black
你知道你可以加一个红黑的
endpoint to this that knows how to take
知道如何服用的终点
an existing set of instances out of
现有的一组实例
discovery and you know puts another one
发现，你知道把另一个
in or reverses it if you you know if you
如果知道，则将其反转
don't like the results you could add
不喜欢您可以添加的结果
kind of a basic a really poor man's form
一种基本的非常贫穷的人的形式
of canary and automated canary analysis
金丝雀和自动金丝雀分析
to this so it's a really interesting
为此，这真的很有趣
choice and I think a wise choice that
选择，我认为一个明智的选择是
was made on how to implement this
关于如何实现这一点
okay let's not do that so we do want it
好吧，我们不要这样做，所以我们确实想要它
since we're going to be jumping we're
因为我们要跳，所以我们
going to jump from Eureka now it's a
要从尤里卡跳下来，现在
client-side load balancing before we
客户端负载均衡之前
move on to the next subject are there
进入下一个主题
any questions in the audience
观众中的任何问题
thus far about service discovery why you
到目前为止，关于服务发现的原因
would use it etc yeah
会用它等等
so for zoo keeper that was actually
所以对于 Zookeeper 来说
initially looked at as as a wave to
最初被视为对
manage discovery we just found that it
管理发现，我们刚刚发现它
didn't scale extremely well and the
没有很好地扩展，
stability of it at the time was a little
当时的稳定性有点差
bit questionable so you know for a
有点可疑，所以你知道一个
hundred instances or a thousand
一百个实例或一千个实例
instances that may not be a big deal
实例可能没什么大不了的
when it's the tens of thousands of
当数以万计的时候
instances that became a maintenance
成为维护的实例
issue more than anything else so that
比什么都重要
was that was the genesis of discovery of
那是发现的起源
Eureka sorry we should mention also
尤里卡（Eureka）抱歉，我们也要提一下
along those lines and I don't think I
按照这些思路，我不认为我
mentioned this earlier it should be
前面提到过这应该是
apparent from this diagram we showed
从这张图可以明显看出
that that Eureka is a central point of
尤里卡是
failure here in your your whole
整个失败
microscopes and architecture so it's
显微镜和建筑，所以
it's critical that you don't just have
至关重要的是，您不仅要拥有
one instance of this running for us we
这样的例子为我们运行
have we operate in multiple Amazon
我们在多个亚马逊运营吗
regions and in every availability zone
地区和每个可用区域
within those regions and we have at
在这些区域内，我们在
least one Eureka server running in every
每个服务器至少运行一台Eureka服务器
availability zone in every Amazon region
每个亚马逊地区的可用区
that we run in and since Eureka is
我们因为尤里卡（Eureka）
designed to be fault tolerant and
设计为容错的
distributed it's you know basically what
分发，基本上你知道什么
we'll always have a Eureka server that
我们将永远有一个Eureka服务器
your service can talk to yeah
您的服务可以与您交谈
I hopefully it is just upgrading the
我希望这只是升级
spring boot and spring cloud versions it
Spring Boot和Spring Cloud版本
all depends on how good of a job we do
一切都取决于我们的工作水平
on spring cloud and getting those
在 Spring 的云上，得到那些
interfaces defined and seeing what our
定义的接口，看看我们
common patterns that that should be
应该是的常见模式
cross-cutting across the different
跨领域交叉
discovery mechanisms so we're showing
发现机制，所以我们展示
responding to status changed events
响应状态更改事件
hopefully that becomes part of a core
希望这成为核心的一部分
interface that console will also support
控制台还将支持的界面
and we'll just make that across the
我们将在整个
board you know you're gonna work so you
登上你知道你会工作，所以你
don't have to worry about it
不用担心
but that would be the goal and that's
但这就是目标，那就是
that's why we like spring boot Netflix
这就是为什么我们喜欢Spring Boot Netflix
isn't likely to move off of Eureka to
不太可能从尤里卡迁移到
console it is very likely to move from
控制台很可能从
here we go one year we go to so even for
我们去这里一年，所以即使
us internally the pain of that we want
我们内部想要的痛苦
to make as minimal as possible am i
使我尽可能地少
understanding about our internal
对我们内部的了解
migration from v1 to v2 of Auriga is
从Auriga的v1迁移到v2是
that you know v2 the v2 server will
您知道v2，v2服务器将
report instances that were registered
报告已注册的实例
with the b1 server and so you kind of
与b1服务器，所以你有点
have a time there where you have both
有时间在那里
versions of the service running and you
您正在运行的服务版本
know potential you have a mixture of
知道潜在的你有混合
clients and you as you move your way
客户和您，随心所欲
towards me - yes
对我-是的
not not truly because we still do uzo
不是真的，因为我们仍在做uzo
bees occasionally oh I'm sorry
蜜蜂偶尔哦，对不起
he's asking if there we think there was
他问我们是否认为那里
anything we lost and when we took a
我们失去的一切，当我们采取
Obie's out of the picture and truth be
奥比不在画面中，事实是
told there are many instances of
告诉有很多事例
applications in Netflix that just using
Netflix中仅使用的应用程序
the OB because it's simpler they don't
OB，因为它更简单，他们不
need a lot of round-robin routing
需要很多循环路由
discovery stuff sometimes we just use
有时我们只是使用发现的东西
route 53 because we know there's only
53号公路，因为我们知道只有
one or two instances that tends to be
一两个实例往往是
more tools than production applications
比生产应用程序更多的工具
because once you get to the point where
因为一旦你到达了
I'm gonna stand up a thousand instances
我要站起来一千个实例
of a thing and do red black we're going
一件事情，做红黑，我们要
to go the Eureka route instead and to
改走尤里卡路线，然后
add to that I mean to be honest the
另外，我的意思是说实话
there's a historical argument against
历史上有反对
elby's that isn't as true today as it
Elby的今天还不如现在
once was when we were operating in ec2
曾经是当我们在ec2中运行时
classic it was almost impossible to
经典，几乎是不可能的
privatize a neo be so that you know it
将新个体私有化，以便您知道
wasn't exposed to the rest of the world
没有接触到世界其他地方
that's no longer true and VPC but we had
VPC不再如此，但是我们有了
already gone down the route of
已经走了
client-side load balancing and we've
客户端负载平衡，我们已经
discovered other benefits to client-side
发现了客户端的其他好处
load balancing that we'll show you in
负载均衡，我们将向您展示
just a little bit that even today with
即使今天，
the OBS and V PC you don't get so I
OBS和V PC却没有，所以我
think we kind of like accidentally fell
认为我们有点像意外跌倒
into it and now we're happy that we did
进入它，现在我们很高兴我们做了
no no we still use we still use route 53
不，不，我们仍在使用，我们仍在使用路线53
and and internally we have the config to
并且在内部，我们有配置
go across each of the each of the Eureka
穿过每个尤里卡
the Eureka instances the server
Eureka实例服务器
instances so it's just route 53 to a
实例，所以它只是到53的路线
well-known DNS name and really a handful
众所周知的DNS名称，确实很少
of them because we have one for each
其中的一个，因为我们每个都有一个
availability zone and for each region
可用区和每个区域
but that stuff's all kind of baked into
但是这些东西都烤成了
our our core deployment when we push
当我们推动我们的核心部署时
something into an ASG on the base ami we
在基础ami上将一些东西放到ASG中
have just environment variables that
只有环境变量
will set those properties for you
将为您设置这些属性
because that we know what's the most
因为我们知道最重要的是
appropriate Eureka endpoint for you to
适合您的Eureka端点
use it's the one in your region in your
使用它是您所在区域中的那个
availability zone all right
可用区好
they did at least the way we were
他们至少按照我们的方式
running internally that would be a
在内部运行，这将是一个
configurable thing but we currently do
可配置的东西，但我们目前正在做
that yes yeah the data is shared
是的，是的，数据是共享的
it's not a full replication it's it's
这不是完整的复制，而是
gonna be partial so it's gonna be split
会变得不完整所以会被分裂
across in number of nodes however many
跨节点数量，但是很多
you want that replication factor that be
你想要那个复制因子
but yeah we do we do keep that and it
但是，是的，我们确实做到了
may be worth noting that data as it
可能值得注意这些数据
stands today is currently all of it
今天就站了
shipped to the client in Eureka one so
运到尤里卡的客户之一
Eureka on my local machine knows about
我本地计算机上的Eureka知道
the status of all the other instances
其他所有实例的状态
that's the big improvement of Eureka two
那是尤里卡二号的最大改进
is reducing that footprint and being
正在减少足迹，
able to subscribe to interested servers
能够订阅感兴趣的服务器
instead of just the entire server farm
而不是整个服务器场
so definitely look forward to Eureka too
所以绝对也期待尤里卡
as soon as it's ready we'll be rolling
一旦准备好，我们将滚动
that out with spring cloud just for that
用 Spring 的云就可以了
benefit alone the yeah
单单受益
and we've hit we've hit on a couple
而且我们已经击中了几个
points here on Eureka I mean it is an
我在尤里卡（Eureka）上的要点是
eventually consistent distributed system
最终一致的分布式系统
so that has some ramifications when you
所以当你
go to do a delivery pipeline and you
去做一个传递管道，你
want to use something like red black
想要使用类似红黑色的东西
pusher or you know some sort of canary
推杆，或者你知道某种金丝雀
analysis process you pretty much have to
分析过程，您几乎必须
accept that your old version of the
接受您的旧版本
service and the new version of service
服务和新版本的服务
are for a time going to be operating
有一段时间要开始运作
simultaneously and that has some
同时有一些
implications for how you develop your
对您如何发展自己的意义
services those services need to be
这些服务需要
stateless those services need to be able
这些服务必须是无状态的
to accept these kind of changes which
接受这些变化
means your services probably also need
意味着您的服务可能也需要
to take you know quicker incremental
让您更快地了解增量
changes rather than than massive changes
变化，而不是大规模的变化
when you go from version to version
当您从一个版本转到另一个版本
speaking from the billing and payments
从帐单和付款中讲
team that's not an easy adoption for
团队不容易采用
everyone to make or wrap your head
每个人都做出或包裹你的头
around using going from a transactional
围绕使用事务性
system to a non non relational
非关系的系统
non-transactional eventually consistent
非交易最终一致
model when you're dealing with money
处理金钱时的榜样
it's not easy
这并不容易
don't don't think it is it won't be a
不要以为那不会是一个
simple conversion but it is worthwhile
简单的转换，但值得
it's definitely the right thing after
之后绝对是正确的事情
we've done it that's that's the opinion
我们做到了，这就是意见
all right
好吧
well we're gonna move on to load client
好，我们要继续加载客户端
side load balancing we're going to show
我们将展示侧面负载平衡
you how to integrate ribbon
你如何整合功能区
and some of the some of the pieces about
还有一些关于
that but first of all I do need to
那但首先我需要
satisfy a bet here you know Taylor and I
在这里打赌，你知道泰勒和我
have been going back and forth on the
一直在来回
the famous question of the the brace
大括号的著名问题
whether it should be on the next line or
是应该在下一行还是
on the prior line so I wish I had
在上一行，所以我希望
something to bribe you with that's
贿赂你的东西
feedback for the conference organizers
对会议组织者的反馈
next time when you drink tickets so I
下次你喝票的时候我
can bribe people but who would like the
可以贿赂人们，但谁愿意
brace on the same line that's
支撑在同一行上
overwhelming Taylor that's overwhelming
泰勒那压倒性的
thank you I agree it's objectively
谢谢，我同意这是客观的
better yeah so the first bit to the two
更好，所以这两个的第一位
two ribbing integration is we're just
两个罗纹的融合是我们只是
going to remove this this override that
将要删除此覆盖该
we have on rest template and we're gonna
我们有休息模板，我们要
what spring cloud do what it does best
Spring Cloud最擅长的是什么
and Auto configure stuff for us behind
和自动为我们配置东西
the scenes unbeknownst to us so we're
我们不知道的场景，所以我们
gonna remove that rest template and what
要删除其余模板以及什么
we're gonna get instead is we're gonna
我们要得到的是我们要
get an auto wire dressed template that's
得到一个自动电线修饰的模板
already configured to work with with
已经配置为与
Eureka so we can at this point we can
尤里卡，所以我们现在可以
replace this hard-coded DNS name with a
将此硬编码的DNS名称替换为
virtual host name that we've set up so
我们这样设置的虚拟主机名
the virtual host name by default is just
默认情况下，虚拟主机名是
this application name and we can refer
这个应用程序的名称，我们可以参考
to it that way I never knew I always
这样我就永远不知道
knew PowerPoint was annoying but I
知道PowerPoint很烦人，但我
didn't know would keep showing up
不知道会继续出现
between as I was trying to tab between
正如我试图在之间
things it really wants to interject
它真正想要插入的东西
itself back into this presentation and
自己回到本演示文稿中，
we're just not going to accept that so
我们只是不会接受所以
yeah now the the service is running
是的，现在该服务正在运行
again
再次
and you see that the result is the same
你会看到结果是一样的
so now we're no longer using a
所以现在我们不再使用
hard-coded address we're using a virtual
我们使用虚拟地址的硬编码地址
host name and we're able to do that
主机名，我们能够做到这一点
about so we talked a little bit about
关于，所以我们谈了一点
the the benefits of client-side load
客户端负载的好处
balancing as opposed to al B's and I'm
平衡，而不是B和我
going to give you a couple concrete
给你几个具体的
examples that are already baked into
已经烤成的例子
ribbon open source so you're everybody's
功能区开放源码，所以您就是每个人的
familiar with like the round-robin type
熟悉如循环式
strategy or maybe like a geolocation
策略或地理位置定位
type strategy a few of the other ones
类型策略，其他一些
ribbon gives you by default are there's
功能区默认为您提供
one called a zone a zone avoidance rule
一个称为防区规则的区域
so imagine you have nine services of an
因此，假设您有一个
application running in in AWS region US
在美国AWS区域中运行的应用程序
East one three of them running in
东其中三分之二
availability zone a three of them
可用区中的三个
running an availability zone B three of
运行以下三个可用区B
them running an availability zone see if
他们运行一个可用区，看看是否
a client of that service keeps executing
该服务的客户端不断执行
requests against the three instances
针对这三个实例的请求
that are running in availability zone a
在可用区a中运行的
and they keep returning you know bad
他们不断回头，你知道不好
results the globe balancer can infer
结果地球平衡器可以推断
that there's probably something wrong
可能有问题
with that availability zone and so
与该可用区等
rather than just round-robin over all
而不是整个循环
nine available instances it can say I'm
可以说我是九个可用实例
gonna start preferring these other two
要开始偏爱这另外两个
availability zones over here for a while
此处的可用区有一段时间
until we see availability zone a start
直到我们看到可用区开始
to heal a second one could be an
治愈第二个可能是一个
availability filter rule on your circuit
电路上的可用性过滤器规则
breaker trips so again if you have a set
如果您有断路器，断路器会再次跳闸
of five services two of which have open
五项服务中的两项，其中两项已开放
circuit breakers right now and they're
断路器，现在
falling back on their fall backs three
跌倒在他们的背上三
of which are returning normally I'm
其中正常返回我
going to give preferential treatment to
将给予优惠待遇
those three that are operating normally
这三个运行正常
as opposed to those that are giving me
而不是那些给我的
the fall backs and the third one would
后退，第三个
just be that the load balancer can keep
只是负载均衡器可以保持
track of the response times and give
跟踪响应时间并给出
preferential treatment to those
对那些人的优惠
instances that respond the most quickly
响应最快的实例
it seems like a very common-sense thing
似乎是很常识的事情
to do the and you know it's important to
去做，你知道重要的是
note that with with ribbon you can
请注意，使用色带可以
compose these various rules together so
将这些各种规则组合在一起
I could have a give preferential
我可以给个优惠
treatment to instances with the fastest
以最快的速度处理实例
response times
响应时间
add the zone avoidance rule as well and
同时添加区域回避规则，并
you can plug in your own your own load
您可以自己插入负载
balancing strategies by just
公正地平衡策略
implementing the I rural interface and
实施I农村接口并
configuring it appropriately so a lot
进行了大量适当的配置
more flexibility and what you can do in
更大的灵活性以及您可以做什么
terms of load balancing that you could
您可以进行的负载平衡条款
ever do with just an e lb or route 53
曾经只用e lb或路线53
all right
好吧
the last thing we have to note about
我们要注意的最后一件事
ribbon and I think this is kind of a
丝带，我认为这有点像
hidden feature that's not a parent it's
不是父项的隐藏功能
not a parent from the beginning is
从一开始不是父母
whenever you're using ribbon or whenever
无论何时使用色带或何时
you've got a ribbon enabled rest
您已经启用了功能区
template there's already a retry
模板已经重试
mechanism built in so if you've got two
内置的机制，如果您有两个
instances of a service running and one
服务正在运行的实例和一个
is down and one is up and your
跌了，一个就涨了，你的
particular client request goes against
特定的客户要求违背
the one that's down there's a
下来的那个有一个
configurable property to say retry and
可配置属性，表示重试和
number of times and more than likely you
次数，甚至更多
depending on what your rule is the first
取决于您的规则是第一个
one's gonna fail it's gonna try the
一个人会失败，它将尝试
second instance RT for you so that's
第二实例RT为您服务
baked into ribbon don't think in those
烤成丝带不要在那些
terms when we get to history only
仅当我们进入历史时的术语
forgets mind you we don't do that for
忘记了你我们不这样做
posts or puts or deletes that would be a
发布或放置或删除将是
little bit dangerous
有点危险
that is an option you can configure if
这是您可以配置的选项
you choose to go that route but it's
您选择走那条路线，但这是
probably not a great idea all right
可能不是一个好主意
see how we're going on time and whether
看看我们如何准时，以及是否
or not we want to talk about paying or
我们是否要谈论支付或
not I say we skip it although we should
不是我说虽然我们应该跳过它
ask does anyone here use fame yes
问这里有人有成名吗
Thank You Spencer so feign internally is
谢谢斯宾塞，所以在内部是假装
not used a lot of Netflix it doesn't
没有使用很多Netflix，它没有
have a whole lot of support internally
内部有很多支持
and we're trying to just see if that's
我们正在尝试看看是否
appropriate or not trying to get a
适当还是不尝试获得
measure of what the Community Interest
衡量社区利益的标准
is why you like fame why you think we
这就是为什么你喜欢名望，为什么你认为我们
should you know keep using that so
你应该知道继续使用吗
anyone who raised their hands and has an
任何举手并有
opinion upon that please come up after
对此的意见请稍后
and tell us we definitely want to know
告诉我们我们绝对想知道
what you like about it what features
您喜欢它的什么功能
it's missing what kind of support it
缺少什么样的支持
should continue to get in the future
将来会继续发展
since it's so quick to demo we won't we
因为演示如此之快，我们不会
won't cut it out for you the we're
不会为您剪裁我们
familiars right now with this form of
现在熟悉这种形式的
rust template call now rest template
锈模板调用现在休息模板
gift for object and right now we're
作为礼物的礼物，现在我们
using a virtual host name or a VIP
使用虚拟主机名或VIP
address here to invoke the other service
在此处寻址以调用其他服务
what this would look like with feign is
假装的样子是
you would you would enable fame clients
你会启用成名的客户
so again the same pattern added
所以再次添加相同的模式
dependency add an annotation to enable
依赖项添加注释以启用
the feature and then you're off to the
功能，然后您就可以
races and we could define a fame client
比赛，我们可以定义成名的客户
and we'll call this membership
我们称这个会员
repository for now and we'll say that
现在我们会说
this is against the Membership virtual
这违反了会员资格
host
主办
and the reason I that I think it doesn't
以及我认为没有的原因
find a lot of adoption any longer at
找到更多的采用
Netflix is because what you see us doing
Netflix是因为您看到我们在做什么
here is configuring more or less the
这里配置或多或少
same set of things that we had to
我们必须做的同样的事情
configure when we just used rest or the
配置我们何时使用休息或
rest template straight up
其余模板直接
so we fain will provide you know an
所以我们很乐意为您提供
automatic implementation of membership
自动执行会员资格
repository for you and you could replace
为您准备的存储库，您可以替换
this rest template call if I injected
这个休息模板调用，如果我注入
you know an instance of a fain client
你知道一个客户的实例
here with
在这里
so that's basically Fame for you it just
所以对你来说基本上就是成名
kind of adds another layer of
有点增加另一层
abstraction between something calling a
所谓的东西之间的抽象
service and the actual call sight so
服务和实际呼叫视线
like TR said it's this library isn't
就像TR所说的，这不是图书馆
really maintained by anybody at Netflix
真正由Netflix的任何人维护
anymore but it's out there stable use it
不再，但它在那里稳定使用
at your discretion for now we'll remove
您现在可以自行决定将其删除
this piece and put things back the way
这块，把事情放回去
they were all nice and tidy any
他们都很好而且很整洁
questions about load balancing while
有关负载均衡的问题
we're on the subject of load balancing
我们正在研究负载平衡
client side load balancing I think we
客户端负载均衡我想我们
got them all out of the way with Eureka
与尤里卡（Eureka）一起解决了所有问题
so we'll move on over to history now
所以我们现在要回到历史
yeah yeah yes
是的，是的
that's right the question was to to get
没错，问题是要得到
ribbon involved here you did nothing and
丝带在这里你什么也没做
that's that's pretty much true there's a
那几乎是真的，有一个
there's a lot more sophisticated use
有很多更复杂的用途
cases you can imagine I mean set that
你可以想象我的意思是
retry policy set the you know what
重试策略设置您知道什么
methods you accept on all you know this
您所知道的所有方法
configuration you can drive that through
配置可以通过
properties files or some external
属性文件或一些外部
configuration management system so the
配置管理系统
code does not change from the example we
代码与我们的示例相同
started with right from the beginning
从头开始
based business logic and nothing else
基于业务逻辑，仅此而已
spring boot everything you should
spring boot 一切你应该
already know we're gonna make very very
已经知道我们会变得非常非常
few if any changes to turn this into
几乎没有任何变化将其转变为
what it looks like internally on that
内部的样子
fleece so we're moving on to the next
摇粒绒，所以我们继续下一个
piece here which is which is histories
这里的那是历史
now hystrix I'm gonna start resolving
现在hystrix我要开始解决
appendices over here and then we're
附录在这里，然后我们
gonna show a quick picture of the
会快速展示一下
canonical example of histories usage
历史用法的典型例子
they like to tell to newcomers to the
他们喜欢告诉新来的人
Netflix ecosystem so we when you see
Netflix生态系统，所以当您看到
this when you log into Netflix is home
当您登录Netflix时，此按钮为
screen you see a list of lists of movies
屏幕上您会看到电影列表的列表
you call it so it's a low Bobo if you
你叫它，所以它是一个低Bobo，如果你
can pronounce that and the low LUMO is
可以说和低LUMO是
provided it's personalized for you so we
只要为您量身定制，我们
watch your viewing history and you know
观看您的观看记录，您就会知道
your demographics and stuff like that
您的受众特征之类的东西
and we try to present a list of titles
我们尝试提供标题列表
that we believe that you want to see if
我们相信您想看看
for some reason so there's a historic
由于某种原因，有一个历史
circuit breaker around retrieving your
回收您的断路器
personalized recommendations for a
个性化推荐
particular row and if that circuit
特定的行，如果该电路
breaker trips for whatever reason we
断路器因任何原因跳闸
can't retrieve your personal results
无法获取您的个人结果
we're gonna follow you back on a set of
我们将跟随您返回一组
of you know commonly you know popular
你们当中的人通常都知道受欢迎
movies that that we think yeah there's
我们认为是的电影
there's a shot that they'll watch one of
有一个镜头，他们会看
these and so that's I think that's the
这些，所以我认为那是
the the example you can keep in mind
您可以记住的示例
when you think of history and whether
当你想到历史以及是否
it's appropriate to use or not in your
是否适合在您的手机中使用
case when you think of something like a
当您想到类似
payment system
支付系统
there's not really a really great
真的不是真的很棒
fallback to getting paid so you know
退还给您的工资，所以您知道
history isn't appropriate everywhere but
历史并不适合任何地方，但
there's certainly uses for it
肯定有用途
many good uses for it so to recap we had
有很多很好的用途，所以回顾一下
at the dependency over here and we will
在这里的依赖，我们将
you could just about guess it right
你大概猜对了
we're gonna enable hystrix and to be
我们将启用hystrix并成为
fair you could say a naval circuit
公平的你可以说一个海军巡回赛
breaker thank you Thank You Spencer or
断路器谢谢你谢谢你斯宾塞或
Dave for being so abstract and your
戴夫这么抽象，你
treatment at this
在这个治疗
hey we're Netflix first we're gonna say
嘿，我们首先是Netflix，我们要说
enable history why not and at this point
启用历史记录为何不这样，此时
we're gonna we're going to start by
我们将要开始
adding a decent fallback so a fallback
添加一个体面的后备，所以一个后备
for a set of movies recommended to you
为您推荐一套电影
by age maybe it's gotta have the same
按年龄可能有相同的
signature by the way as the original
原始签名
method might be just a set of movies
方法可能只是一组电影
they're like family recommendations good
他们就像家人的推荐一样好
for all ages so we're gonna say like
对于所有年龄段的人，我们都会说
movies like the Sandlot everybody loves
每个人都喜欢的电影如Sandlot
that one right hook
那一个右钩子
you know that's safe for all ages and
你知道这对所有年龄段的人都是安全的
we're gonna return that set of movies as
我们将把那部电影作为
our fallback and here up in our request
我们的后备以及我们的要求
mapping we're gonna add a history
映射我们要添加历史记录
command itself and we're gonna say
命令自己，我们要说
so this would be it this would be the
所以这就是这将是
the the basic you know as simple as it
您知道的最简单的基础
can get history command configuration
可以获取历史命令配置
right here you're you're just specifying
就在这里，您只是在指定
a fallback and whenever any exception is
后备，只要有异常
thrown from this this implementation
从此实现抛出
right here it's going to go back to the
就在这里，它会回到
fallback so in our case if we're not
回退，所以在我们的情况下，如果我们不
able to find the user we're gonna go to
能够找到我们要去的用户
the fallback if we're you know the
如果我们知道您的后备
membership service was down we're gonna
会员服务下降，我们要
go to the fallback we're gonna have one
进行后备，我们将拥有一个
more thing here which is a I think very
我想这是更多的事情
commonly found when we use histories
我们在使用历史记录时通常会发现
internally at Netflix and that's the
在Netflix内部，那就是
let's put this up here because I cheat
我们把它放在这里，因为我作弊
you know it's shameless but but I cheat
你知道那是无耻的，但是我作弊
and that's just a timeout so we're gonna
那只是一个超时，所以我们要
say that whenever the implementation of
说，每当执行
this method takes more than a certain
这种方法不仅需要
amount of time we're going to just go to
我们要去的时间
the fallback so we're gonna say if it
回退，所以我们要说
takes more than five seconds for you to
需要五秒钟以上的时间
find a member forget it
找一个成员算了
I'm just gonna give you the family
我要给你一家人
recommendations and move on along this
建议并继续前进
is an important thing because when you
是一件重要的事情，因为当你
have a string of Micra service calls one
有一串Micra服务电话
to another and there's some service
到另一个，有一些服务
that's its way down the line that starts
这就是开始的路线
misbehaving that's not responding very
表现不佳
quickly that adds up I mean that
快速加起来，我的意思是
propagates all the way up to the front
一直传播到最前面
end so at each level you know there
结束，所以在每个级别上您都知道
should be an expectation about you know
应该是对你的期望
what the the response time for the next
下一个响应时间是多少
level service down should be and in that
服务水平应该在
way you don't you know you don't
你不知道的方式
queue up a bunch of requests that are
排队一堆的请求
potentially never going to finish and
可能永远不会完成，
just and just toss your whole system all
公正地将整个系统抛诸脑后
right so
对吧
and internally it doesn't take long for
在内部不需要很长时间
someone to find when you've done this
完成此操作后找人
when you've created a dependency on an
当您创建对
external service without hystrix around
外部服务不需加注音
it it'll bubble up to someone really
它会冒泡给某人
quickly and they will come find you and
很快，他们就会来找你，
let you know sorry you probably should
让您知道抱歉，您可能应该
wrap that so very commonly used I guess
包裹这么非常常用的我猜
I need to provide a yeah once again in
我需要再次同意
my life I thought it was the computers
我以为是电脑
fault than it was mine yeah how many
比我的错还好耶
times I have to Rove of that moment
那个时候我不得不去狂欢
again we're gonna run Rex it's worth
再次，我们要经营雷克斯，这值得
putting out if you haven't seen the
如果您还没有看到
membership service that's running in the
正在运行的会员服务
background right now we've just injected
现在我们刚刚注入背景
some arbitrary latency it's on a
一些任意的延迟
standard deviation so some requests will
标准偏差，因此有些要求会
take longer than others some requests
比其他人花费更长的时间
will arbitrarily fail about two percent
会任意失败约百分之二
will just return a 500 just so we can
只会返回500，所以我们可以
demo some of this
演示一些
I'm also starting another sample
我也在开始另一个样本
application that's available in their
他们可以使用的应用程序
repository and it is just just stupid
仓库，它只是愚蠢的
simple is the history dashboard so what
简单的历史记录仪表板是什么
we've done with the history command is
我们用history命令完成的是
this application is now collecting up
该应用程序现在正在收集
information about every history command
有关每个历史记录命令的信息
that's invoked and it's making it
被调用并且正在实现
available as a stream the history
作为流历史可用
dashboard we're going to use to connect
我们将用于连接的仪表板
to that stream whoops so here we're at
到那流stream，所以我们在这里
the the history dashboard page and we'll
历史记录仪表板页面，我们将
go to localhost a do 1 which is where
转到localhost a do 1，这是哪里
our recommendation service is running
我们的推荐服务正在运行
and we'll just say history starts stream
我们只说历史开始
and then we're going to start abusing it
然后我们将开始滥用它
with jmeter
与jmeter
and what you see here is as the abuse
你在这里看到的是虐待
starts and this isn't necessary good
开始，这没有必要好
history example but you see that when
历史示例，但您看到
the latency gets too large and the
延迟过大，
requests are failing the circuit will
请求失败，电路将
temporarily open but you know for the
暂时开放，但您知道
most parts close with it and what you
大多数零件都与它以及您所关
really want to do is find a threshold
真正想做的就是找到一个门槛
where where your circuit is generally
通常您的电路在哪里
closed unless there's some exception
除非有例外，否则关闭
condition handle happening in this case
在这种情况下发生的条件句柄
the circuit is opening because of that
电路因此断开
timeout interval that we that we
超时间隔我们
specified just to show you that that it
指定只是为了向您表明
opens and closes then responses are
打开和关闭，然后响应是
still coming through recommendations and
仍在通过建议和
whenever you see it open you're gonna be
每当你看到它打开时，你都会
watching hook and seeing a lot for the
看钩子，看到很多
rest of the weekend so if we saw this
周末剩下的时间，所以如果我们看到这个
behavior in production that'd be
生产中的行为
indicative of some poorly tuned history
指示一些历史不佳的历史
settings so your latency is not in line
设置，以免延迟
with your expected timeout settings so
与您的预期超时设置一样
we actually track this case and find
我们实际上跟踪了这种情况并找到了
them help people retune those those
他们帮助人们重新调整那些
configurations there's one other thing
配置还有另一件事
we think it's important to know about
我们认为了解这一点很重要
history and that's that fundamentally
历史，这就是根本
it's it's executing by default anyway
它是默认情况下执行的
it's executing the contents of any
它正在执行任何内容
history command inside of a thread pool
线程池内的history命令
which means if you've got any code in
这意味着如果您有任何代码
there that depends on thread locals or
那里取决于线程本地或
you've got like an app transactional
你就像一个事务性的应用程序
attribute things start going sideways
属性事情开始横盘整理
pretty quick so we're gonna I'm going to
很快，我们要去
show you what that would would would
告诉你那会怎样
look like we're going to use an existing
看起来我们将使用现有的
cross context holder dot current request
跨上下文持有者点当前请求
attributes Thank You Taylor for your
属性谢谢泰勒为您
spring trivia he happens to know that
Spring 琐事，他碰巧知道
that uses a thread local yes if you're
如果您正在使用本地线程
not familiar it's just gonna pull any
不熟悉，只会拉任何东西
information from the current request
当前请求中的信息
bounds of the threat so we like to use
威胁的范围，所以我们喜欢使用
this in the data layer to grab things
这个在数据层抢东西
like request params that say page size I
像要求参数说页面大小我
don't want to pass page size all the way
不想一直传递页面大小
through my application so here's a
通过我的应用程序，所以这是一个
convenient way to get access to it right
正确访问它的便捷方法
up until you wrap it in history yeah and
直到您将其包装在历史中，是的，
this should normally be fine getting the
这通常应该很好
current request attributes as a natural
当前请求属性自然
thing
事情
to want to do
想做
but actually there should be one right
但实际上应该有一项权利
there you'll see that this exception got
在那里，您会看到此异常
thrown an exception was no thread bound
引发异常没有线程绑定
for you know etc etc and you can see
你知道等等等等，你可以看到
right here that in the stack trace that
就在这里，在堆栈中跟踪
hysteresis was involved in in preventing
迟滞涉及预防
this throughout local from functioning
这是整个地方的运作
correctly so there is there is a
正确，所以有一个
workaround of sorts but it has a it has
各种解决方法，但是它有一个
some ramifications in this case we can
在这种情况下，我们可以
say execution dot isolation dot strategy
说执行点隔离点策略
and we want its value to be semaphore
我们希望它的价值是信号量
basically it means that the cut it's
基本上，这意味着削减
just going to lock here in this in this
只是要锁定在这里
body rather than farming off this work
身体而不是耕种这项工作
to a thread pool that operates outside
到在外部运行的线程池
of it which means this request will
这意味着该请求将
function now transactional will function
现在交易将起作用
correctly but if for example this
正确，但是如果例如
membership service was taking an
会员服务正在
extremely long time to run the thread
运行线程的时间非常长
that's running that request is now
现在正在运行该请求
blocked until that request returns so
在该请求返回之前被阻止，因此
there's a trade-off here if you want to
如果您想在这里进行权衡
use history and transactional or history
使用历史和交易或历史
and thread local type things together
并将本地类型的东西放在一起
you have to accept you know potentially
你必须接受你可能知道的东西
hung threads it's it's something we
挂线，这是我们的事
don't really have a workaround for at
真的没有解决方法
this point yet but we're definitely once
至此，但我们肯定是一次
once we discovered it and notice it was
一旦我们发现它，发现它是
a problem it's something we're gonna
一个问题，这是我们要去的事情
look at just building a bridge for the
看只是为
inheritable threat local from spring
从 Spring 开始本地可遗传的威胁
which most everything uses so it's an
大多数东西都用它，所以
implementation that hasn't been solved
尚未解决的实现
yet but something to be aware of if
但是，要注意的是
you're currently using this alright so
您当前正在使用此功能，因此
we'll take this out
我们把这个拿出来
are there any questions about history
关于历史有任何疑问吗
I I couldn't hear it sorry sorry can't
我听不到，对不起，对不起
you just try speaking up a little bit
你只是试着说一点
yes
是
I mean thatthat sinto Thalia up to your
我是说那个罪过塔利亚，取决于你
application logic so he's asking for
应用逻辑，所以他要
chained dependency services how do we
链式依赖服务我们如何
how does the service at the front end
前端的服务如何
decide what the fallback should be for
决定后备的用途
something weighed further down the
东西压得更重了
simple and easy answer is it just tries
简单容易的答案就是尝试
its best so depending on what your
最好，这取决于您的
service is if you're a recommendation
服务是您的推荐
service fall back is easy there's not
服务回退很容易，没有
much pain there if you're in the payment
如果您要付款，那会很痛苦
space you know and you have a service
您知道并提供服务的空间
that's responsive for returning price no
这对退货价格有反应
there there is no fallback you just you
没有后备，只有你
just throw an exception history still
仍然抛出异常历史记录
has value in blocking those long running
具有阻止长时间运行的价值
stuck threads so that you don't waste
卡住线程，以免浪费
time calling my broken service but there
时间打电话给我坏了的服务，但在那里
certainly isn't a a reasonable fallback
当然不是合理的后备
there's a more complicated answer that
还有一个更复杂的答案
we're not going to touch on completely
我们不会完全谈及
today but I can tell you is coming and
今天，但我可以告诉你，
that is deep tagging of the requests so
这是对请求的深度标记
you can know where something came from
您可以知道某物从何而来
where it failed that way when the
当它以这种方式失败的地方
fallback comes up to the top-level
回退到最高层
service you can know the difference
服务你可以知道区别
between a failure at something in the
在某件事情的失败之间
middle tier versus something in the
中间层与
deeper levels or deeper and deeper so
更深层次或更深层次
you can choose oh the the building
你可以选择建筑物
services down there's no point showing
下来的服务没有意义
you this page let me render something
你这个页面让我渲染一些东西
different that's that's a project called
不同的是那个项目叫做
sell and fit and there's there's two or
出售和装配，有两个或
three different internal projects
三个不同的内部项目
related to that exact thing that we
与我们确切的事情有关
expect to be open sourcing sometime next
期望在下一个时间开放采购
year I will mention one other pattern
一年，我会提到另一种模式
and I don't and I'd say this with some
我不会，我会和一些人这样说
reservation but internally at Netflix
保留但在Netflix内部
our clients are not always our service
我们的客户并不总是我们的服务
clients are not always as thin as you
客户并不总是像你一样瘦
might imagine so rather than executing
可能会这样想，而不是执行
rest requests directly to the service
休息请求直接向服务
like you see here oftentimes the
就像您经常在这里看到的
services accompanied by a client library
客户库附带的服务
and that client library will sometimes
该客户端库有时
provide the history commands and fall
提供历史命令并倒下
backs and so forth so basically the same
背等基本相同
team that's you know providing the
您知道的团队提供
service can also provide some of the
服务还可以提供一些
fallback strategies yeah
后备策略是的
so I'll show you one of the tools today
因此，我将向您展示其中一种工具
at the end of this talk Atlas it's it's
在本演讲的最后，Atlas是
our operational tool and history it's
我们的操作工具和历史
definitely goes there we still have this
肯定去那里我们仍然有这个
dashboard to consume it a little more
仪表板多消耗一点
visually but for real ops stuff and
视觉上，但真正的操作的东西和
monitoring we we consume it out of atlas
监控我们从地图集中消耗掉它
and we are going to skip turbine today
今天我们要跳过涡轮
we were going to demo that but turbine
我们本来要演示的，但是涡轮
allows you to aggregate several services
允许您汇总几个服务
history extremes into one and then then
历史极端融为一体，然后
you can basically display a combined
你基本上可以显示一个组合
dashboard as well so there's also that
仪表板也是如此
option out there for you it still exists
选项在那里，它仍然存在
it still runs I can say I've maybe gone
它仍然运行我可以说我可能已经走了
to it once or twice and three years of
一次或两次，三年
being a Netflix it's it's more useful
成为Netflix更有用
probably to everyone here who's just
可能对这里的每个人来说
getting started doesn't have the complex
入门没有复杂
back-end like Atlas and just wants to
像Atlas这样的后端，只想
keep track you know maybe you only have
跟踪，您知道也许您只有
a few hundred services but you can see
几百种服务，但您可以看到
from the UI it doesn't scale well to the
从用户界面无法很好地扩展到
tens of thousands you need something a
成千上万的你需要一些东西
little more fine-grained a little more
多一点细一点多一点
tunable so it we ought grew it
可调，所以我们应该把它长大
essentially yes
本质上是
so how does history play a role in in
那么历史如何在
failures and and load balancing of rest
故障和其余负载的平衡
calls so we mentioned ribbon has
电话，所以我们提到功能区有
different load balancing strategies one
不同的负载均衡策略之一
of them is history's aware so it is
他们当中有历史知道
aware of the fact that I am calling a
知道我在打电话给我
downstream service that is having a
具有以下功能的下游服务
problem it has a history circuit breaker
问题，它有一个历史断路器
that is open and what it will do is will
那是开放的，它将要做的是
just not send traffic to that node
只是不向该节点发送流量
hopefully it's not all of the nodes so
希望不是所有的节点，所以
if it's an isolated problem your circuit
如果这是一个孤立的问题，您的电路
breaker is open in one availability zone
断路器在一个可用区中打开
then ribbon will shift all of that
然后色带将转移所有这些
traffic to one of the other zones that
流量到其他区域之一
are healthier there there's a there's a
更健康，那里有一个
great like I I don't think it's
像我这样伟大的人不认为这是
apocryphal I think it's a true story
我认为这是一个真实的故事
about the Superbowl and you know so
关于超级碗，你知道的
we're operating in a realm that's AWS
我们在AWS领域中运营
we've got auto scaling groups for auto
我们有自动缩放组
scaling up for auto scaling down you
放大以自动缩小您
know trying to be efficient about
知道要提高效率
resources and so forth and then the
资源等等，然后
Super Bowl starts and everybody will use
超级碗开始，每个人都将使用
Netflix like everybody stop watching
像所有人一样的Netflix停止观看
Netflix because they're watching the
Netflix，因为他们正在观看
Super Bowl
超级碗
and so our aSG's are looking around and
因此我们的aSG正在四处寻找
going hey you know I guess we don't have
嘿，你知道我猜我们没有
any more traffic we're gonna start
我们要开始的更多流量
scaling ourself down and then halftime
缩小自己，然后半场休息
hits and this you know I'm like most
点击，你知道我最喜欢
halftime shows it's horrible and and
半场时间表明这太可怕了，并且
everybody comes back to Netflix it
每个人都回到Netflix
starts watching Netflix again at a
开始在再次观看Netflix
halftime and so they call it the
半场，所以他们称之为
Thundering Herd you know we just get
雷群，你知道我们刚得到
slammed with a with a sudden influx of
突然涌入
traffic this is where you know circuit
交通这是你知道的地方
breakers might start opening because
断路器可能开始断开，因为
timeouts aren't men anymore but this
超时不再是男人了，但这
illustrates that a lot of times circuit
说明了很多次的电路
breakers are being open for some
断路器正在向一些人开放
temporary condition like in this case
像这种情况下的暂时状况
our ASG s are now rapidly trying to
我们的ASG正在迅速尝试
scale themselves up and what's this once
扩大规模，这又是什么
it's back you know like once we've
回到我们知道的时候
scaled back up again those circuit
再次放大那些电路
breakers you're going to start closing
断路器，您将要开始合闸
again and things are going to heal
再次，一切都会好起来的
themselves if we didn't have the history
自己，如果我们没有历史
circuit you know this sir we would never
巡回赛，你知道这个先生，我们永远不会
recover because all those requests would
之所以能够恢复，是因为所有这些请求都会
have backed up and and we would have
已经备份，我们将有
gone nowhere especially when you get
一无所获，特别是当你得到
into things like retry policies which is
像重试政策这样的东西
a default configuration of ribbon you
功能区的默认配置
know I call a service it fails
知道我称服务失败
let me just call five more times and see
我再打五遍看看
I might get lucky when we have an issue
我们遇到问题时可能会很幸运
of thundering herd when services are
服务时的雷电群
legitimately down that just makes the
合理地下降只会使
situation worse we already can't scale
情况更糟，我们已经无法扩展
up the demand and the demand just
满足需求和需求
increased fivefold because of our retry
由于我们的重试而增加了五倍
strategy so that's really the sweet spot
策略，所以这真的是最佳选择
for history this is just cutting that
对于历史，这只是削减
off letting the services kind of settle
让服务类解决
down just stopping the traffic from the
下来只是阻止来自
source and then you can scale up as
源，然后您可以按比例放大
things start to look healthy again
事情又开始恢复健康
hystrix will let one request through if
hystrix将让一个请求通过
it's still bad keep the rest away if it
它仍然很糟糕
starts to look good start opening the
开始看起来不错，开始打开
gates let more people come through yeah
大门让更多人通过
I've heard that before you know history
我听说过，在您了解历史之前
was really fully there we had a lot of
真的很满，我们有很多
like if Superbowl type checks and the
例如超级碗类型检查和
code do X because it got bad enough so
代码做X因为它已经够坏了，所以
yeah it's interesting
是的，这很有趣
electrics sure metrics so I mean we've
电气指标，所以我的意思是
talked about a few things I point it out
谈到一些我指出的事情
some some history timings that they may
一些可能的历史时机
not be tuned very well when you go to
去的时候调不好
this micro service architecture and we
这种微服务架构，我们
start talking about tens or hundreds of
开始谈论数十或数百
services of one application type talking
一种应用程序类型的服务对话
to just as many of a different
一样多
application type so I can do just as
应用程序类型，因此我可以像
many and you start getting to a point
很多，你开始达到目的
where every public method on an API
API上的每个公共方法
might as well be its own new micro
可能是它自己的新微型
service you really start to lose track
您真的开始迷路了
of what's going on
发生了什么
so metrics becomes critical to that kind
因此指标对于此类至关重要
of thing it's it's a good architecture
事情是一个好的架构
to have there are a lot of benefits to
有很多好处
it but you have to be prepared for that
它，但你必须为此做好准备
so what we're gonna show today is the
所以我们今天要展示的是
metrics library that we primarily use
我们主要使用的指标库
internally it's called spectator if
在内部它称为旁观者
that's confusing because you know a
这令人困惑，因为您知道
library called servo which is also the
称为伺服的库，也是
Netflix metrics library yeah spectator
Netflix指标库是观众
wraps servo and just a cleaner more
包裹伺服器，更清洁
dependency injection friendly test
依赖注入友好测试
friendly API so spring cloud currently
友好的API，因此Spring Cloud目前
uses servo that is an incoming pull
使用伺服器作为传入拉力
request to just flip it over to the
要求将其翻转到
spectator and clean up a few nasty bits
观众并清理一些令人讨厌的地方
along the way so we're just gonna go
一路走，所以我们要走了
ahead and add that dependency
并添加该依赖项
so spectators support always has
所以观众的支持总是
dependency spectator support is being
依赖观众支持
provided by the the contrib library
由contrib库提供
right now just to be clear so there's an
现在只是要清楚，所以有一个
auto configuration on the presence of
存在时自动配置
certain classes from spectator and so
观众的某些班级等等
forth so like I said we expect this'll
就像我说的那样，我们希望这会
be full you can integrate it into spring
充满你可以将其整合到 Spring
claude before too long there's actually
不久之后，
a little family of dependencies because
一些依赖的家庭，因为
we didn't get around to making a starter
我们没有去做一个初学者
yet but naturally you would have a
但是，自然地，你会有一个
spring but-- spectator starter or spring
Spring ，但是-观众的发车人或 Spring
cloud spectators starter so we're gonna
云观众首发，所以我们要
pull those dependencies in and we're
拉那些依赖，我们
gonna talk a little bit while that's
会聊一点
going about how spectator is structured
关于观众的结构
versus how the existing spring boot
与现有的 spring boot 如何
metrics library is or something else you
指标库是您还是其他人
might be using so this is primarily a
可能正在使用，所以这主要是
tag driven dimensional metrics api so if
标记驱动的维度指标api，如果
you're familiar with graphite or
您熟悉石墨或
something similar a metric is a name
类似指标的名称
it's a string if you want to pull
这是一个字符串，如果你想拉
dimensions out of it it usually involves
它通常涉及的尺寸
parsing that string something like rest
解析该字符串像休息
dot service or URL dot 200 that's this
点服务或URL点200就是这个
rest call to this service was successful
对该服务的其余电话成功
there's another one for failure another
还有一个因为失败而另一个
one for 404
404个
so those parsing rules get a little
所以那些解析规则会有点
complicated right everyone has to be on
每个人都必须面对的复杂权利
the same page everyone has to follow the
每个人都必须遵循的同一页面
same pattern it works it's just not
它的工作原理相同，只是没有
discoverable so instead of that we've
可发现的，而不是我们
opted for more tag driven architecture
选择更多的标签驱动架构
so just to show an example I'm going to
因此，为了说明一个例子，我将要
actually I need an order water
其实我需要点水
Spectator registry again by that Netflix
Netflix再次向观众注册
contribs library this is just going to
contribs库，这只是要
be created automatically when spectators
当观众自动创建
on your class path there's nothing you
在你上课的路上，你什么都没有
need to do so we can just law like a
需要这样做，我们可以像
simple metric say let's do a count of
简单的指标说让我们做一个
mmm recommendations and let's start
mmm建议，让我们开始吧
tagging it success false that's it you
标记成功为假，就是你
can put as many tags as you want on that
可以在上面放置任意数量的标签
as far out as you can handle it's
尽你所能
perfectly fine there's some caveats some
很好，有一些警告
things you don't want to put his tags
你不想放他标签的东西
say maybe a customer ID or user name or
说出客户ID或用户名，或者
those those will blow up very quickly
那些会很快爆炸
and and we'll mention why that's
而且我们会提到为什么
important to know shortly but just keep
重要的是要很快知道，但要保持
that in mind you should be careful with
请记住，您应该注意
what you tag so we'll say that is true I
您标记了什么，所以我们会说是对的
haven't anything
没什么
yep stop there's
是的，停在那里
okay and there's one piece of
好吧，有一件
housekeeping that I of course forgot
我当然忘了家务
this is again why we're putting this out
这就是为什么我们要把这个放出来
before we do an actual pull request
在我们进行实际拉取请求之前
there are some things that just conflict
有些事情只是冲突
so this does not play nicely currently
所以目前播放效果不好
with the existing spring cloud servo
与现有的Spring 云伺服器
integrations something we're aware of
我们知道的整合
and going to tweak
并进行调整
so I'm gonna kick off my jmeter let's
所以我要开始我的jmeter，让我们
get some traffic going and let's go over
吸引一些流量，让我们过去
to the spring boot metrics actuator so
到Spring 启动指标执行器
we can see a bunch of default statistics
我们可以看到大量的默认统计信息
that we've been added that have been
我们被添加了
added by our contribs library but just
由我们的contribs库添加，但是
let's find the I apologize I did miss
让我们找到我想念的道歉
one thing I have registered a counter I
一件事我已经注册了柜台
have not actually incremented the
实际上并没有增加
counter that is pretty useless I think
我觉得那没用
you did that earlier tonight it is a
你今晚早些时候做了
common thing it's it's a nice API but it
常见的是它是一个不错的API，但是
does leave some room for error
确实留有一些错误的余地
smally searching for that one we've made
smally寻找我们制造的那个
kind of a best effort here at mapping
在映射上尽了最大的努力
the tag based metric to a quote unquote
基于标签的度量标准，以取消引用
hierarchical name basically it's just
层次名称基本上就是
the rest of the metric name followed by
其余指标名称，后跟
set of parentheses and like I said of
套括号，就像我说的
arguments that have all the tags in it
带有所有标签的参数
and we've sorted the tags for you and so
我们已经为您整理了标签，因此
forth so they appear a reasonable worker
如此看来他们是一个合理的工人
but in general trying to take a
但一般来说，
hierarchical metric name and mapping it
分层度量标准名称并将其映射
to a tag name means you need to know the
标签名称意味着您需要了解
specifics about that domain
有关该域的详细信息
you know this exactly how the the pieces
你知道这是如何碎片
of that hierarchy are are structured so
该层次结构的结构如此
there's no generic hierarchical to tag
没有通用的层次结构可以标记
based mapping that you can imagine
您可以想象的基于映射
unfortunately may be experiencing bed
不幸的是可能正在床上
demo look for some reason it's very odd
演示出于某种原因很奇怪
that this one metric would fire and not
该指标会触发而不会
the rest oh because I foolishly went to
剩下的哦，因为我愚蠢地去了
the wrong service
错误的服务
area recommendations find me yes success
推荐地区，我觉得是成功
true success false and do we have
真正的成功是错误的，我们有吗
traffic we do not have traffic
交通我们没有交通
there we go so we are getting about this
我们去了所以我们正在解决这个问题
is a normalized rate second of this
是此的归一化速率秒
metric so for the success false
度量标准，因此成功不正确
condition the fall back we are getting
条件回退，我们得到
about eighty four failures per second
每秒约八十四次失败
for the good condition we're getting
为了获得良好的状态
about three per second so we're off and
大约每秒三秒钟，所以我们出发了
running we're gathering metrics this
运行我们正在收集指标
shouldn't look too unfamiliar if you've
如果您已经不应该看起来太陌生
used any other metrics library it's the
使用了其他任何指标库
one we choose because it plays nicely
我们选择一种，因为它表现出色
with our back end so just to see what
与我们的后端，所以只是看看
other metrics we've captured out of the
我们从中捕获的其他指标
box first off would be every single
首先是盒子
request mapping so we've just created a
请求映射，所以我们刚刚创建了一个
spectator auto configuration
观众自动配置
if you have registry on the classpath
如果您在类路径上有注册表
we'll build that for you as you've seen
如您所见，我们将为您打造
if you are a web application we'll build
如果您是网络应用程序，我们将构建
an interceptor for you and that's gonna
一个拦截器给你，那会
just catch every request and tag a few
只是捕获每个请求并标记一些
common things what was the method of the
常见的事情是什么方法
request what was the URI template
请求什么是URI模板
variable are the URI template that was
变量是以前的URI模板
used so we're gonna take the name
用过的，所以我们取这个名字
variables and substitute them you won't
变量并替换它们，您不会
get the customer ID so no metrics
获取客户ID，因此没有指标
explosions you'll just get - customer ID
您将获得的爆炸-客户ID
- can grab the handler names so the
-可以获取处理程序名称，因此
method names in MVC who called you if
在MVC中调用您的方法名称
you have a notion or a custom header
您有一个概念或自定义标题
that determines who called you this is
确定谁叫你这个
just property driven you can go ahead
只是财产驱动，你可以继续
and set that if an exception was thrown
并设置是否抛出异常
what was the type of the exception and
什么是例外类型？
what was the response code status so
响应代码的状态如何？
these are the things we needed
这些是我们需要的东西
internally we just finally shipped it
在内部，我们终于发货了
out to the rest of the world because
销往世界其他地方，因为
these are the common everyday we always
这些是我们每天常有的日子
want to know and you'll see I registered
想知道，你会看到我注册了
this a little bit differently I used
这与我以前使用的有点不同
what's called a a bucket timer so in
所谓的桶式计时器
addition to just recording the counts of
除了只记录
executions of this this will record the
执行此操作将记录
time of execution and then add some
执行时间，然后添加一些
special tags and those tags are the
特殊标签，这些标签是
buckets so it'll break in the break the
桶，所以它会打破打破
tags up into five groups by default and
默认将标签分为五个组，
that's triggered by this max age so if
这是由这个最大年龄触发的，所以如果
we go back and look at our metrics you
我们回头看看我们的指标
can see I have status 200 client abort
可以看到我的状态为200客户中止
exception
例外
how's that yeah yeah we have the count
怎么样，是的，我们有数
bucketed in one second bucket in two
一秒钟一桶
seconds bucketed in five seconds rate
以五秒为单位的秒数
per second so you can see we're quickly
每秒，所以您可以看到我们很快
just ramping up the amount of data
只是增加了数据量
collection we're getting - we've got
我们得到的收藏-我们有
lots of good details but we're still not
很多好的细节，但我们仍然没有
quite ready to put it together yet just
准备好将其放在一起
to show some the other things we have
展示我们拥有的其他一些东西
the exact same thing for any rest
休息时完全一样
template
模板
we had to do a little magic to get the
我们必须做一点魔术才能得到
actual input the URL templates so that
实际输入网址模板，以便
when you did a rest call we could figure
你打个电话的时候我们可以算
out you know this is the customer ID
你知道这是客户ID
this is the user name so we have a
这是用户名，所以我们有一个
little aspect wrapping that and we're
包装的小方面，我们
going to capture your much the same data
将捕获您几乎相同的数据
method URL template status client name
方法URL模板状态客户端名称
in this case membership and then the
在这种情况下，成员资格然后
actual time of it and we've taken this
它的实际时间，我们已经采取了
and we've done it as well for spring
我们在 Spring 也做了
integration which I'll just show I think
我将展示的整合
that's running on
正在运行
so of new in spring integration for two
所以在 Spring Integration 了两个
there's a great new metric subtraction
有一个很棒的新指标
and we just couldn't let that slide so
我们不能让那张幻灯片如此
we immediately pulled that in and
我们立即将其拉入
configured the same thing so you'll have
配置了相同的东西，因此您将拥有
the the name be spring integration and
名称是spring integration和
we'll have the the type of the thing it
我们将得到事物的类型
was being a transformer a channel a Polo
曾经是Polo频道的变压器
channel a cue channel and then from each
引导提示频道，然后从每个
of those the metrics that went through
这些经历的指标中
so Netflix can trips we're gonna we're
以便Netflix可以绊倒我们
gonna publish all of this data for you
将为您发布所有这些数据
you don't have to figure it out metrics
您不必弄清楚指标
for free on probably the most common
免费可能是最常见的
things that you deal with things to do
您要处理的事情
our cue handlers message mapping
我们的提示处理程序消息映射
endpoints those are all going to be
端点都将成为
added in the future because we need them
将来添加，因为我们需要它们
internally so that's Spectator any
在内部，所以任何观众
questions on spectator itself sure
观众本身的问题肯定
yes
是
that's fair fair enough
足够公平了
so he was just correcting correctly
所以他只是正确地纠正
pointing out that the the notion of tags
指出标签的概念
here is not quite the same as what what
这与什么不完全一样
it might be in something like open TS TV
可能是在开放式TS电视中
another framework that kind of fits in
另一种适合的框架
the same role so these are truly
同样的角色，所以这些都是真正的
dimensions they're fully fleshed out for
他们完全充实的尺寸
each one we're going to take all of this
每一个我们都将接受所有这些
data and ship it to our back-end where
数据并将其运送到我们的后端
in other frameworks so that stuff is
在其他框架中，这样的东西是
kind of collapsed down so things like
倒塌了，所以像
customer ID are dangerous because of the
客户ID很危险，因为
high cardinality because it's just too
基数高，因为它也是
much data to ship to the backend
大量数据要发送到后端
if you want to use
如果你想使用
so we are taking the Dakota Hale metrics
因此我们采用了达科他州黑尔州的指标
and stuffing them into spectator and
塞进观众
they're getting shipped but like I said
他们正在发货，但是就像我说的
I mean in general taking a hierarchical
我的意思是一般来说
name and transforming it into a tag
名称并将其转换为标签
based name has its limits so we're doing
基于名称的限制，所以我们正在做
that to an extent it remains to be seen
在一定程度上还有待观察
how useful that actually is but if you
这实际上有多有用，但是如果您
publish something under the spring boot
在 spring boot 下发布一些东西
metrics framework be a coda Hale or
指标框架可以是Coda Hale或
something else you've come up with we'll
您想出的其他东西，我们会
go in you know there's an aggregator
进去就知道有一个聚合器
interface we'll take those and publish
界面，我们将采用这些并发布
them to the spectator for what use it
他们给观众什么用
maybe we'll try to see people take one
也许我们会尝试看到人们采取一个
more question we got a show Atlas with
更多的问题，我们得到了一个展示图集
the little time remaining we've got
剩下的时间很少
yeah not from spectator itself because
是不是来自观众本身，因为
spectator is just an API to gather data
观众只是一个收集数据的API
keep it up in memory and then do
将其保存在内存中，然后执行
something with that do something with is
与某事做某事是
what we haven't gotten to yet but this
我们还没有达到的目标
this will just store in memory purged
这只会存储在清除的内存中
over time and if no one uses it it just
随着时间的流逝，如果没有人使用它，
goes away but it this is the full data
消失了，但这是完整的数据
so if you do some really crazy
所以如果你做一些非常疯狂的事情
dimensions or crazy amount of metrics it
尺寸或疯狂的指标
may be a problem it's not something
可能是一个问题，这不是问题
we've seen but it's certainly something
我们已经看到了，但这肯定是
you could set up for yourself now we
您现在可以为自己设置
need to talk about the back end so
需要谈论后端，所以
just make sure it's running so what we
只要确保它正在运行，那么我们
have is a service called Atlas please
请提供一项名为Atlas的服务
check it out in github the documentation
在github文档中查看
I'm going to keep here because it is
我要留在这里，因为
helpful to show some of this stuff but
有助于显示其中一些内容，但
we're running it in a local
我们在本地运行
configuration in memory there's a start
内存中的配置有个开始
Atlas script in the root of our projects
项目根源中的Atlas脚本
just feel free to give it a run and
随便跑吧
watch it go for you and what we need is
看着它适合你，我们需要的是
one final plugin
一个最终的插件
the reason what the membership
会员的原因
so this dependency is the the plugin
所以这个依赖就是插件
that takes data collected by I spectator
接收我观众收集的数据
and ships it to the backend so the
并将其运送到后端，因此
aggregation you were talking about is
您正在谈论的汇总是
what's gonna happen on the backend after
之后后端会发生什么
each of the separate instances ship all
每个单独的实例都会全部运送
their data to the backend and I get
他们的数据到后端，我得到
Netflix Contrave is going to configure
Netflix Contrave将进行配置
it set it up for you
它为您设置
there are still some properties you need
仍然需要一些属性
to have just like with Eureka
和尤里卡一样
and that property is the location of the
该属性是
Atlas your eye where to publish it to
将您的眼睛发布到哪​​里
and the same rules apply as with Yuriko
和Yuriko的规则相同
we tend to start with route 53 and maybe
我们倾向于从53号路线开始，也许
do some some more load balancing beyond
再做一些负载均衡
that route 53 fits perfectly for
那条路线53非常适合
something like Atlas being just a tool
像Atlas这样的工具
when it's not as important to us
当它对我们不那么重要时
rerun recommendations now that we have
现在重新运行建议
the dependency
依赖
that's not good
这不好
so if I look at my Atlas it's collected
所以如果我看我的地图集
some data from a couple of apps
来自几个应用程序的一些数据
membership and now recommendations is
成员资格，现在的建议是
showing as well so this is the tag API
同时显示，所以这是标签API
we can start discovering things about
我们可以开始发现有关
our dimensions that are better in Atlas
我们在Atlas中更好的尺寸
from here so I've shown app name maybe I
从这里开始，所以我已经显示了应用名称
want to see bucket what buckets exist
想看一下桶里有什么桶
maybe I want to see URI
也许我想看URI
here the your eyes that have been
这是你的眼睛
collected by spectator and published out
由观众收集并发布
to Atlas so we have some good access to
到Atlas，因此我们可以轻松访问
this data here so now we have the
这些数据在这里，所以现在我们有了
information but what's the purpose of
信息，但目的是什么
all this and that really is to put it
所有这一切，实际上就是说
somewhere that is visual so let's go
可见的地方，让我们开始吧
ahead and run a different URL so this is
并运行一个不同的URL，所以这是
v1 graph query parameter is name comma
v1图形查询参数是名称逗号
rest equal comma average so there we go
休息等于逗号平均，所以我们去
we have some data coming from Atlas
我们有一些来自阿特拉斯的数据
already just graphing what we have on
已经在画我们所拥有的
the back end so this is this reverse
后端，所以这是反向
polish notation this is the the way
波兰符号是这样
they've decided to implement all of the
他们决定实施所有
Atlas queries it's a little daunting at
Atlas质疑这有点令人生畏
first look but it's actually very nice
乍一看，但实际上非常好
to have all this wrapped in the URL
将所有内容包装在URL中
pattern so that you can forward these
模式，以便您可以转发这些
links as image links and they just go
链接作为图像链接，它们就走了
they fit anywhere you can go forward
它们适合您可以前进的任何地方
backwards everything is nice and
向后一切都很好，
workable so okay fine we have a line on
可行，好吧，我们在线上
a graph let's uh let's go a little bit
图表让我们继续吧
deeper so I'm looking at the rest
更深，所以我在看剩下的
statistic we were seeing spring spring
我们看到 Spring 的统计数据
Netflix contrition I'm going to get the
Netflix的贡献我要去
count
计数
hopefully I type that right
希望我输入正确
I think alice's just being a little bit
我想爱丽丝只是有点
slow for us
对我们慢
my poor machine yeah this instance has
我的机器很糟糕，这个实例有
had about enough request timeout that's
大约有足够的请求超时
not good I'm just gonna go ahead and
不好，我只是继续前进，
give Atlas a little bounce
给阿特拉斯一点反弹
because I think it's had enough
因为我觉得已经受够了
it's unfortunate we're going to lose
不幸的是我们要输
this historical metrics we've been
我们一直以来的历史指标
gaining so far but that's okay
到目前为止到目前为止，但是还可以
the demo curse indeed
演示诅咒的确
you have to restart the services
您必须重新启动服务
and just see if
然后看看
this works so one of the things we did
这行得通，所以我们做的一件事
just building on that API library is we
只是建立在该API库上
just collapsed a few examples into this
只是把几个例子弄成这样
dashboard about HTML just so that you
有关HTML的信息中心，以便您
can see
可以看到
there we go so as these metrics build up
随着这些指标的建立，我们去了
over time we're gonna see this one is
随着时间的流逝，我们会看到这是
just looking at the rate by time bucket
只是按时段查看汇率
so we have about 100 per second running
所以我们每秒运行约100次
off the road a meter the vast majority
路上一米绝大多数
of them are in the one second bucket
他们在一秒钟内
very small minority is in the two second
很小的一部分在两秒钟内
bucket even fewer in the five second
在五秒钟内就更少了
bucket so that's that normal
桶，那是正常的
distribution we talked about for our
我们为我们讨论的发行
random latency but you can kind of sort
随机延迟，但您可以进行某种排序
of get a grasp on how we can just pull
了解我们如何才能拉
this stuff together and turn it into
一起把它变成
something that's a little more
还有一点
consumable something that's visual you
易消耗品
can get your hands on very quickly this
可以很快上手
dashboard took me a very little time to
仪表板花了我很少的时间
get through so here's the same thing
通过，所以这是同一件事
rate by bucket and handler name so let's
通过存储桶和处理程序名称进行评分，让我们
just put those two dimensions together
只是把这两个维度放在一起
let's see if there's one method that's
让我们看看是否有一种方法是
performing a little better a little
表现好一点
worse than the other we actually have a
比其他人更糟糕，我们实际上有一个
team there reliability engineering team
团队在那里可靠性工程团队
they mostly focus on just playing with
他们主要集中在玩
this discovering metrics tweaking them
这种发现指标对其进行了调整
by different dimensions and trying to
通过不同的尺寸并尝试
find outliers trying to find which node
查找试图找到哪个节点的异常值
on a farm is going badly which API is
一个农场上的API表现不佳
behaving poorly and even at what times
表现不佳，甚至在什么时候
of the day those things start to go off
那些日子开始消失了
so another one is percentage of response
所以另一个是回应百分比
codes as you can see we had about a two
正如您所看到的，我们大约有两个
percent failure or you might be able to
失败百分比，或者您可能能够
see the tiny sliver of red up at the top
在顶部看到红色的细条
so just a different way to visualize
所以只是一种不同的可视化方式
this stuff as a stacked out of 198
这东西堆积了198
percent we're fine right up until the
百分之百，我们一直很好，直到
very end when we did a little server
当我们做了一个小服务器时非常结束
bounce max time by my handler name so
通过我的处理者姓名弹跳最大时间，因此
you get the idea this is where we can do
您知道这是我们可以做的
some of the alerting stuff so if you
一些警报的东西，所以如果你
refer to the Atlas examples there are
请参考Atlas示例
just so many of these examples on
这些例子很多
putting multiple lines on a pit on a
将多条线放在一个坑上
image putting prediction lines on an
将预测线放在
image taking something that looks like
拍摄看起来像的东西
this very sharp and choppy and using an
这非常尖锐和断断续续，并使用
algorithm double exponential smoothing
算法双指数平滑
to just do a best fit curve that way you
那样做一条最合适的曲线
can see roughly where you are there are
可以大致看到你在哪里
time shift capabilities built in so you
内置的时移功能使您
can shift back and show me a line that
可以向后退并向我显示一条线
is this exact metric from last week or
是上周的确切指标还是
last month that way I can compare the
上个月，我可以比较
two
二
it's just a really really powerful
真的非常强大
back-end and it's it's what actually
后端，这实际上是
drives a lot of our ability to do red
推动我们发挥红色的能力
black pushes to do to be a fail fast
黑推很快就失败了
company to roll billing out and oh wow
公司要推出帐单哦
there's it's broken we need to we need
坏了，我们需要我们需要
to hurry up and react to it so this this
赶快反应吧所以这个
is really one of the core pieces of our
确实是我们的核心部分之一
infrastructure that it's a shame we
我们很遗憾的基础设施
haven't seen more of an open source and
还没有看到更多的开源和
we want to really start pushing it so
我们想真正开始推动它，所以
this is a consumable piece it's
这是一个消耗品
something you can set up with a little
你可以用一点设置的东西
care and it's something that we think
关心，这是我们认为的
spring cloud could use some more of so
Spring 的云可以使用更多
we definitely want to figure out how we
我们绝对想弄清楚我们如何
can push this forward and make this
可以推动并实现这一目标
assumable for everyone great I'll take
对于每个伟大的人我都会承担
questions well connect to the VPN so any
问题很好地连接到VPN，所以任何
questions on Atlas atlas
关于地图集的问题
he was asking when was the Atlas project
他在问Atlas项目是什么时候
started so that was probably maybe three
开始，所以大概是三个
or four years ago it's it's been it's
或四年前它是
been internal for a while incubating I
在孵化我一段时间
think it's been open source for over a
认为它已经开源了
year now what's not open source is the
今年不是开源的
UI we have internally which we're gonna
用户界面，我们将在内部进行
show a little bit of John can connect to
展示约翰的一点点可以连接到
the VPN just so you can get a real feel
VPN就是这样，您才能真正感受到
of what this looks like in inside of
里面的样子
Netflix but it's it's been a long time
Netflix，但是已经很久了
coming and we talked about Eureka but
来了，我们谈论了尤里卡，但是
this is really the thing that separate
这真的是分开的东西
from Eureka is probably the biggest
来自尤里卡的人可能是最大的
piece of our infrastructure that really
我们基础设施的一部分
matters to us day to day it really
对我们来说每天都很重要
enables DevOps
启用DevOps
we did that again is still not open
我们做了一次，仍然没有打开
sourced yet unfortunately but everything
不幸的是来源
in those graph api's are just JSON blobs
在那些图表API中只是JSON Blob
if you if you ask for it not as a PNG
如果您要的不是PNG
but as a JSON you'll get the data points
但是作为JSON，您将获得数据点
so we have just a really simple service
所以我们只有一个非常简单的服务
that trolls those you inform the surface
巨魔你告知表面的那些
what to watch for give it a threshold
注意什么给它一个门槛
and if this JSON value ever goes above
如果此JSON值超过
send an email send a pager duty it's all
发送电子邮件发送传呼机职责
it's all integrated very nicely so it's
都很好地集成了，所以
it's something that has been on the deck
它已经在甲板上了
for a while we need to get out into
有一阵子，我们需要进入
though into the rest of the world
虽然进入了世界其他地区
because it's so good and it really makes
因为它是如此的好，而且确实使
our lives easier well Taylor's bringing
泰勒带给我们的生活更轻松
up his - I mean about the alerting thing
他的-我的意思是关于警报的事情
you know there's alice has a feature for
你知道爱丽丝有一个功能
exponential smoothing of a particular
特定项的指数平滑
curve as well and so you can you can
弯曲，所以你可以
kind of luminate those spurious spikes
可以消除那些虚假的尖峰
and then once we often base alerting
然后一旦我们经常发出警报
triggers off of the the exponential a
触发指数a
smooth curve so you set a certain
平滑的曲线，因此您可以设定
threshold and somebody gets paged so as
门槛，有人分页，以便
I said we've been working on this stuff
我说我们一直在努力
internally the spring integration of
内部的Spring 整合
this this is a dashboard we built and
这是我们构建的仪表板，
it's using all the same metrics we're
它使用所有相同的指标
showing today so you know find me the
今天显示，所以你知道找到我
counts of all the MVC requests and their
所有MVC请求及其数量的计数
Layton sees stack them by bucket and
雷顿（Layton）看到他们用铲斗堆放
just show them on a Dada dashboard that
只需在Dada仪表板上显示它们
makes sense it makes it easily
这很容易做到
consumable so you can see our requests
易耗品，您可以看到我们的要求
were eight and this is for the one of
是八岁，这是为之一
the core billing systems 600 per second
核心计费系统每秒600个
is the average rate you can see this
您可以看到的平均汇率是多少
black line is the rate from last week
黑线是上周的汇率
that's our time shift where you can see
那是我们可以看到的时移
these little interesting dips right last
最后这些有趣的骤降
week on this day there was a bug in prod
在这一天的一周中，产品中存在一个错误
somewhere above us so history kicked in
我们之上的某个地方，历史开始了
our traffic went down we were alerted it
我们的流量下降了，我们收到了警报
wasn't our fault but we knew now we got
不是我们的错，但我们知道现在
on the issue right away identified who's
马上就找出谁是
having the trouble when let them help
让他们帮助时遇到麻烦
them fix it
他们修复它
oh they're interesting patterns you
哦，它们是有趣的图案
might notice is this little spike here
可能会注意到这是一个小尖峰
it coincides with a spike on the black
它与黑色尖峰相吻合
history line as well what that tells me
历史线以及那告诉我的
is actually somebody has a job somewhere
实际上有人在某处工作
at Netflix and is hammering our service
在Netflix并正在努力改善我们的服务
on a given time the same day every day
每天同一天的给定时间
or every week we don't know why yet
还是每个星期我们都不知道为什么
that's a very common thing
这是很平常的事情
I'd say a lot of my day is responding to
我会说我很多时候都在回应
these alerts and graphs and figuring out
这些警报和图表并找出
who is responsible so you saw that
谁负责，所以你看到了
caller metric that is critical here when
来电者指标在此处至关重要
I break this up by caller and I know
我由来电者分解，我知道
it's that service that's the one I need
这就是我需要的服务
to go track down and talk to it's just
去追踪并与之交谈
incredibly helpful and then having these
很有帮助，然后拥有这些
all together with the Layton sees with
所有与雷顿一起看到
the total exceptions logged all the way
一路记录所有异常
down to CPU heaps that's TCP networks
一直到TCP网络的CPU堆
that's putting them all on one dashboard
将它们全部放在一个仪表板上
just really drives home you know when
真的开车回家，你知道什么时候
you're having an issue where is it when
你有什么问题，什么时候
I see a drop in connections and I see a
我发现连接数下降，并且看到
spike in TCP failures I know it's not
TCP故障激增，我知道不是
probably not my code it's probably
可能不是我的代码，可能是
something on Amazon if I see Layton sees
如果我看到雷顿看到的东西在亚马逊上
go up and exceptions go down it just
上升而异常下降
becomes so clear to us what is what is
对我们很清楚什么是什么
going on in fact this is so useful we've
实际上，这是如此有用，我们已经
actually built a language internally
实际上是在内部建立一种语言
around it that's it's a closure based
围绕它是基于闭包的
DSL to build some of those URLs because
DSL建立其中的一些URL，因为
I said it's a little bit daunting but
我说这有点令人生畏，但
again that's something we want to we
同样，这是我们想要的
want to put out into the community so
想要投入社区
that we can get some some traction on
我们可以得到一些牵引力
this framework this is also a great like
这个框架也很棒
behavioral modification tool so you know
行为修改工具，让您知道
like you mentioned before if you if you
就像你之前提到的，如果你
set an alert on you know a particular
对您认识的人发出警报
service anytime it doesn't return an
服务，只要它不返回
HTTP 200 over a certain small threshold
HTTP 200超过某个较小的阈值
somebody can get paged you pretty
有人可以寻呼你漂亮
quickly find that that service starts
迅速发现服务开始
returning to hundreds more often so they
回到更频繁的数百，所以他们
can be really useful for things like
对于诸如
that it's very common to create alerts
创建警报是很常见的
for other teams that cause issues for
对于其他引起问题的团队
you any final questions I know we're
您有任何最后的问题，我知道我们
kind of wrapping up on time here all
一切都按时结束
right well thank you so much for coming
很好，非常感谢您的光临
you
您